var config = [

    /****************************************** 		level 1 ----------- CyberSecurity 		******************************************/
    {level:"1", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "We should turn on .............. to protect Our Computer from hacker.", answers: ["VLC", "Script", "Antivirus", "Firewall"], correct: 4},
    {level:"1", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "What are the elements of cybersecurity?", answers: ["Network Security", "Operational Security", "Application Security", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"1", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "What are the common cyber-attacks which can be used by hackers to damage network?", answers: ["Phising & Password attacks", "Malware & Malvertising", "DDoS & Drive-by downloads", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"1", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Which of the following option is used to protect data and passwords?", answers: ["Authorization", "Authentication", "Encryption", "Non-repudiation"], correct: 3},
    {level:"1", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Which of the following is the first computer virus?", answers: ["Creeper", "Blaster", "Sasser", "None of the above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"1", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Cybersecurity is the protection of?", answers: ["Internet connected systems", "Non-Internet connected systems", "Both A and B", "None of the above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"1", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Cybersecurity also be referred to", answers: ["incident security", "information technology security", "internet security", "threat security"], correct: 2},
    /****************************************** 		level 2 ----------- CyberSecurity		******************************************/
    {level:"2", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Which of the following is one of the Cyber Security Goals?", answers: ["Protect the confidentiality of data", "Preserve the integrity of data", "Promote the availability of data for authorized users", "All of the above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"2", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "In cybersecurity, what does CIA stand for?", answers: ["Confidentiality, Confidentiality, Availability", "Central, Intelligence, Agency", "Cybersecurity, Investigation, Agency", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 1},
    {level:"2", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Cybersecurity Protect against what?", answers: ["Unauthorised Access", "Unauthorised Deletion", "Unauthorised Modification", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "When integrity is lacking in a security system, _________ occurs.", answers: ["Database hacking", "Data deletion", "Data tampering", "Data leakage"], correct: 3},
    {level:"2", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Cybersecurity is primarily about?", answers: ["technologies", "processes", "Both a and b", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 3},
    {level:"2", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "What are the key features of Cybersecurity?", answers: ["Vulnerability", "Threat", "Risk", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "According to the CIA Triad, which of the below-mentioned element is not considered in the triad?", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Authenticity", "Availability", "Integrity"], correct: 2},
    /****************************************** 		level 3 ----------- CyberSecurity		******************************************/
    {level:"3", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "When you use the word _____ it means you are protecting your data from getting disclosed.", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Authentication", "Availabilit"], correct: 1},
    {level:"3", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "______ means the protection of data from modification by unknown users", answers: [" Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Availability", " Non-repudiation"], correct: 2},
    {level:"3", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Cybersecurity encompass the full range of?", answers: ["vulnerability reduction", "incident response", "recovery policies", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"3", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Which of the following information security technology is used for avoiding browser-based hacking?", answers: ["Anti-malware in browsers", "Remote browser access", "Adware remover in browsers", "Incognito mode in a browser"], correct: 2},
    {level:"3", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "In which year, the first computer worm (virus) created?", answers: ["1969", "1971", "1970", "1973"], correct: 3},
    {level:"3", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "This helps in identifying the origin of information and authentic user. This referred to here as ________", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Authenticity", "Availability"], correct: 3},
    {level:"3", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Using _____________ for doing competitive information gathering is a crime.", answers: ["Spyware", "Antivirus", "Anti-malware", "Adware"], correct: 1},
    /****************************************** 		level 4 ----------- CyberSecurity 		******************************************/
    {level:"4", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Which of the following is one of the Cyber Security Goals?", answers: ["Protect the confidentiality of data", "Preserve the integrity of data", "Promote the availability of data for authorized users", "All of the above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "In cybersecurity, what does CIA stand for?", answers: ["Confidentiality, Confidentiality, Availability", "Central, Intelligence, Agency", "Cybersecurity, Investigation, Agency", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Cybersecurity Protect against what?", answers: ["Unauthorised Access", "Unauthorised Deletion", "Unauthorised Modification", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "When integrity is lacking in a security system, _________ occurs.", answers: ["Database hacking", "Data deletion", "Data tampering", "Data leakage"], correct: 3},
    {level:"4", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "What are the common cyber-attacks which can be used by hackers to damage network?", answers: ["Phising & Password attacks", "Malware & Malvertising", "DDoS & Drive-by downloads", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Which of the following option is used to protect data and passwords?", answers: ["Authorization", "Authentication", "Encryption", "Non-repudiation"], correct: 3},
    {level:"4", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Which of the following is the first computer virus?", answers: ["Creeper", "Blaster", "Sasser", "None of the above"], correct: 1},
    /****************************************** 		level 5 ----------- CyberSecurity		******************************************/
    {level:"5", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "When you use the word _____ it means you are protecting your data from getting disclosed.", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Authentication", "Availabilit"], correct: 1},
    {level:"5", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "______ means the protection of data from modification by unknown users", answers: [" Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Availability", " Non-repudiation"], correct: 2},
    {level:"5", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Cybersecurity encompass the full range of?", answers: ["vulnerability reduction", "incident response", "recovery policies", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"5", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Which of the following information security technology is used for avoiding browser-based hacking?", answers: ["Anti-malware in browsers", "Remote browser access", "Adware remover in browsers", "Incognito mode in a browser"], correct: 2},
    {level:"5", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "In which year, the first computer worm (virus) created?", answers: ["1969", "1971", "1970", "1973"], correct: 3},
    {level:"5", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "This helps in identifying the origin of information and authentic user. This referred to here as ________", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Authenticity", "Availability"], correct: 3},
    {level:"5", theme: "CyberSecurity", question: "Using _____________ for doing competitive information gathering is a crime.", answers: ["Spyware", "Antivirus", "Anti-malware", "Adware"], correct: 1},


    
    /****************************************** 		level 1 ----------- Fundamentals 		******************************************/
    {level:"1", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Which is not a part of cyber attacks?", answers: ["bullying", "Malvertising", "MITM", "Ransomeware"], correct: 1},
    {level:"1", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Cybersecurity includes _______ ?", answers: ["Application Security", "Disaster Security", "Operational Security", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"1", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "what types of attacks made on Confidentiality?", answers: ["Cracking encrypted Data", "Doxxing", "Both a and b", "None of the above"], correct: 3},
    {level:"1", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "what types of attacks made on Integrity?", answers: ["Web Penetration", "Doxxing", "Disrupting Server", "Installing the spyware"], correct: 1},
    {level:"1", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Which is not a part of Countermeasure of Confidentiality attacks?", answers: ["Access control", "Hashing", "Biometric Verification", "Encryption"], correct: 2},
    {level:"1", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "what types of attacks made on Availability?", answers: ["DDoS Attacks", "Ransomeware Attacks", "Disrupting Server", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"1", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "What types of Countermeasure for attacks on availability?", answers: ["Regular Backup", "Cryptography", "Hashing", "Access Control"], correct: 1},
    /****************************************** 		level 2 ----------- Fundamentals 		******************************************/
    {level:"2", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Cybersecurity Protect against what?", answers: ["Unauthorised Access", "Unauthorised Deletion", "Unauthorised Modification", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Which is not a part of Countermeasure of Availability attacks?", answers: ["Data Replication", "Encryption", "Regular Backup", "None of the Above"], correct: 2},
    {level:"2", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "what types of Countermeasure for Integrity attacks?", answers: ["Intrusion Detection", "Hashing", "Both a and b", "None of the Above"], correct: 2},
    {level:"2", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "What are the common cyber-attacks which can be used by hackers to damage network?", answers: ["Phising & Password attacks", "Malware & Malvertising", "DDoS & Drive-by downloads", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "What types of Countermeasure for attacks on availability?", answers: ["Adequate Communication bandwidth", "Regular backup", "Data replication", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "What are the Three pillars of Cybersecurity", answers: ["People, Processes, Technology", "People, Private, Ransomeware", "People, Antivirus, Laws", "None of the Above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"2", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Which of the following is the most important activity in system hacking?", answers: ["Covering Tracks", "Escalating privileges", "Cracking Password", "Information Gathering"], correct: 3},
    /****************************************** 		level 3 ----------- Fundamentals 		******************************************/
    {level:"3", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "What is Code Red?", answers: ["Virus", "Antivirus", "Photo Editing Software", "None of the above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"3", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Which of the following is also known as Malicious software?", answers: ["Badware", "Illegalware", "Malware", "Maliciousware"], correct: 3},
    {level:"3", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "What are the common cyber-attacks which can be used by hackers to damage network? ", answers: ["Phishing & Password attacks", "Malware & Malvertising", "DDoS & Drive-by downloads", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"3", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "A computer virus may be used to -", answers: ["Corrupt data in your computer", "Log the user's keystrokes", "Access private data like user id and passwords", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"3", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Which of the following option is used to protect data and passwords?", answers: ["Authorization", "Authentication", "Non-repudiation", "Encryption"], correct: 4},
    {level:"3", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "What does TCP/ IP stands for?", answers: ["Transaction control protocol / Internal protocol", "Transmission control protocol / Internet protocol", "Transmission contribution protocol / Internal protocol", " None of the above"], correct: 2},
    {level:"3", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Which of the following database is queried by Whois?", answers: ["ARIN", "APNIC", "ICANN", "DNS"], correct: 3},
    /****************************************** 		level 4 ----------- Fundamentals 		******************************************/
    {level:"4", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "what types of attacks made on Integrity?", answers: ["Web Penetration", "Doxxing", "Disrupting Server", "Installing the spyware"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Which is not a part of Countermeasure of Confidentiality attacks?", answers: ["Access control", "Hashing", "Biometric Verification", "Encryption"], correct: 2},
    {level:"4", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "what types of attacks made on Availability?", answers: ["DDoS Attacks", "Ransomeware Attacks", "Disrupting Server", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "What types of Countermeasure for attacks on availability?", answers: ["Regular Backup", "Cryptography", "Hashing", "Access Control"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Cybersecurity Protect against what?", answers: ["Unauthorised Access", "Unauthorised Deletion", "Unauthorised Modification", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Which is not a part of Countermeasure of Availability attacks?", answers: ["Data Replication", "Encryption", "Regular Backup", "None of the Above"], correct: 2},
    {level:"4", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "what types of Countermeasure for Integrity attacks?", answers: ["Intrusion Detection", "Hashing", "Both a and b", "None of the Above"], correct: 2},
    /****************************************** 		level 4 ----------- Fundamentals 		******************************************/
    {level:"5", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Which of the following is one of the Cyber Security Goals?", answers: ["Protect the confidentiality of data", "Preserve the integrity of data", "Promote the availability of data for authorized users", "All of the above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"5", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "In cybersecurity, what does CIA stand for?", answers: ["Confidentiality, Confidentiality, Availability", "Central, Intelligence, Agency", "Cybersecurity, Investigation, Agency", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 1},
    {level:"5", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Cybersecurity Protect against what?", answers: ["Unauthorised Access", "Unauthorised Deletion", "Unauthorised Modification", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"5", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "When integrity is lacking in a security system, _________ occurs.", answers: ["Database hacking", "Data deletion", "Data tampering", "Data leakage"], correct: 3},
    {level:"5", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "Cybersecurity is primarily about?", answers: ["technologies", "processes", "Both a and b", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 3},
    {level:"5", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "What are the key features of Cybersecurity?", answers: ["Vulnerability", "Threat", "Risk", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"5", theme: "Fundamentals", question: "According to the CIA Triad, which of the below-mentioned element is not considered in the triad?", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Authenticity", "Availability", "Integrity"], correct: 2},
    


    /****************************************** 		level 1 ----------- Basics		******************************************/
    {level:"1", theme: "Basics", question: "When you use the word _____ it means you are protecting your data from getting disclosed.", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Authentication", "Availabilit"], correct: 1},
    {level:"1", theme: "Basics", question: "______ means the protection of data from modification by unknown users", answers: [" Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Availability", " Non-repudiation"], correct: 2},
    {level:"1", theme: "Basics", question: "Cybersecurity encompass the full range of?", answers: ["vulnerability reduction", "incident response", "recovery policies", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"1", theme: "Basics", question: "Which of the following information security technology is used for avoiding browser-based hacking?", answers: ["Anti-malware in browsers", "Remote browser access", "Adware remover in browsers", "Incognito mode in a browser"], correct: 2},
    {level:"1", theme: "Basics", question: "In which year, the first computer worm (virus) created?", answers: ["1969", "1971", "1970", "1973"], correct: 3},
    {level:"1", theme: "Basics", question: "This helps in identifying the origin of information and authentic user. This referred to here as ________", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Authenticity", "Availability"], correct: 3},
    {level:"1", theme: "Basics", question: "Using _____________ for doing competitive information gathering is a crime.", answers: ["Spyware", "Antivirus", "Anti-malware", "Adware"], correct: 1},
    /****************************************** 		level 2 ----------- Basics 		******************************************/
    {level:"2", theme: "Basics", question: "Which of the following is one of the Cyber Security Goals?", answers: ["Protect the confidentiality of data", "Preserve the integrity of data", "Promote the availability of data for authorized users", "All of the above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"2", theme: "Basics", question: "In cybersecurity, what does CIA stand for?", answers: ["Confidentiality, Confidentiality, Availability", "Central, Intelligence, Agency", "Cybersecurity, Investigation, Agency", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 1},
    {level:"2", theme: "Basics", question: "Cybersecurity Protect against what?", answers: ["Unauthorised Access", "Unauthorised Deletion", "Unauthorised Modification", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "Basics", question: "When integrity is lacking in a security system, _________ occurs.", answers: ["Database hacking", "Data deletion", "Data tampering", "Data leakage"], correct: 3},
    {level:"2", theme: "Basics", question: "Cybersecurity is primarily about?", answers: ["technologies", "processes", "Both a and b", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 3},
    {level:"2", theme: "Basics", question: "What are the key features of Cybersecurity?", answers: ["Vulnerability", "Threat", "Risk", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "Basics", question: "According to the CIA Triad, which of the below-mentioned element is not considered in the triad?", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Authenticity", "Availability", "Integrity"], correct: 2},
    /****************************************** 		level 3 ----------- Basics 		******************************************/
    {level:"3", theme: "Basics", question: "What is Code Red?", answers: ["Virus", "Antivirus", "Photo Editing Software", "None of the above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"3", theme: "Basics", question: "Which of the following is also known as Malicious software?", answers: ["Badware", "Illegalware", "Malware", "Maliciousware"], correct: 3},
    {level:"3", theme: "Basics", question: "What are the common cyber-attacks which can be used by hackers to damage network? ", answers: ["Phishing & Password attacks", "Malware & Malvertising", "DDoS & Drive-by downloads", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"3", theme: "Basics", question: "A computer virus may be used to -", answers: ["Corrupt data in your computer", "Log the user's keystrokes", "Access private data like user id and passwords", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"3", theme: "Basics", question: "Which of the following option is used to protect data and passwords?", answers: ["Authorization", "Authentication", "Non-repudiation", "Encryption"], correct: 4},
    {level:"3", theme: "Basics", question: "What does TCP/ IP stands for?", answers: ["Transaction control protocol / Internal protocol", "Transmission control protocol / Internet protocol", "Transmission contribution protocol / Internal protocol", " None of the above"], correct: 2},
    {level:"3", theme: "Basics", question: "Which of the following database is queried by Whois?", answers: ["ARIN", "APNIC", "ICANN", "DNS"], correct: 3},
    /****************************************** 		level 4 ----------- Basics 		******************************************/
    {level:"4", theme: "Basics", question: "Cybersecurity Protect against what?", answers: ["Unauthorised Access", "Unauthorised Deletion", "Unauthorised Modification", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "Basics", question: "Which is not a part of Countermeasure of Availability attacks?", answers: ["Data Replication", "Encryption", "Regular Backup", "None of the Above"], correct: 2},
    {level:"4", theme: "Basics", question: "what types of Countermeasure for Integrity attacks?", answers: ["Intrusion Detection", "Hashing", "Both a and b", "None of the Above"], correct: 2},
    {level:"4", theme: "Basics", question: "What are the common cyber-attacks which can be used by hackers to damage network?", answers: ["Phising & Password attacks", "Malware & Malvertising", "DDoS & Drive-by downloads", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "Basics", question: "What types of Countermeasure for attacks on availability?", answers: ["Adequate Communication bandwidth", "Regular backup", "Data replication", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "Basics", question: "What are the Three pillars of Cybersecurity", answers: ["People, Processes, Technology", "People, Private, Ransomeware", "People, Antivirus, Laws", "None of the Above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "Basics", question: "Which of the following is the most important activity in system hacking?", answers: ["Covering Tracks", "Escalating privileges", "Cracking Password", "Information Gathering"], correct: 3},
    /****************************************** 		level 5 ----------- Basics 		******************************************/
    {level:"5", theme: "Basics", question: "Which of the following is one of the Cyber Security Goals?", answers: ["Protect the confidentiality of data", "Preserve the integrity of data", "Promote the availability of data for authorized users", "All of the above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"5", theme: "Basics", question: "In cybersecurity, what does CIA stand for?", answers: ["Confidentiality, Confidentiality, Availability", "Central, Intelligence, Agency", "Cybersecurity, Investigation, Agency", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 1},
    {level:"5", theme: "Basics", question: "Cybersecurity Protect against what?", answers: ["Unauthorised Access", "Unauthorised Deletion", "Unauthorised Modification", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"5", theme: "Basics", question: "When integrity is lacking in a security system, _________ occurs.", answers: ["Database hacking", "Data deletion", "Data tampering", "Data leakage"], correct: 3},
    {level:"5", theme: "Basics", question: "Cybersecurity is primarily about?", answers: ["technologies", "processes", "Both a and b", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 3},
    {level:"5", theme: "Basics", question: "What are the key features of Cybersecurity?", answers: ["Vulnerability", "Threat", "Risk", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"5", theme: "Basics", question: "According to the CIA Triad, which of the below-mentioned element is not considered in the triad?", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Authenticity", "Availability", "Integrity"], correct: 2},
    
    
    /****************************************** 		level 1 ----------- IP_DNS 		******************************************/
    {level:"1", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "What is the format of IP address?", answers: ["34 bit", "64 bit", "16 bit", "32 bit"], correct: 4},
    {level:"1", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "Version 6 of IP address has how many bits.", answers: ["64 bits", "128 bits", "32 bits", "256 bits"], correct: 2},
    {level:"1", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "IANA stands for __________", answers: ["Internet Assigned Numbers Authority", "Internal Assigned Numbers Authority", "Internet Associative Numbers Authoritative", "Internal Associative Numbers Authority"], correct: 1},
    {level:"1", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "How many version /s of IP’s are there?", answers: ["4 Versions", "3 Versions", "2 Versions", "1 version"], correct: 3},
    {level:"1", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "Many desktops and operating systems include which protocol?", answers: ["IPv6 protocol", "IPv4 protocol", "Both IPv6 and IPv4 protocol", "IPv3 protocol"], correct: 1},
    {level:"1", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "The design of the Internet protocol suites adhere to the ________ principle.", answers: ["Data corruption", "End to End principle", "Connection oriented", "Reliability"], correct: 2},
    {level:"1", theme: "IP_DNS", question: " ___________ adjusts the segment size to be smaller than MTU.", answers: ["Internet Protocol 6", "User Datagram Protocol", "Internet Protocol 4", "Transmission Control Protocol"], correct: 4},
    /****************************************** 		level 2 ----------- IP_DNS 		******************************************/
    {level:"2", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "MAC stands for ________", answers: ["Media Area Control", "Memory Access Control", "Memory Area Control", "Media Access Control"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "Hardware address is known as ________", answers: ["MAC address", "IP Address", "Network Interface Card", "Address Resolution Protocol"], correct: 1},
    {level:"2", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "What translates IP address into MAC address?", answers: ["Organizationally Unique Identifier", "Address Resolution Protocol", "Network interface card", "Burned In Address"], correct: 3},
    {level:"2", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "The entire hostname has a maximum of ___________", answers: ["255 characters", "127 characters", "63 characters", "31 characters"], correct: 1},
    {level:"2", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "DNS database contains _______", answers: ["Name server records", "hostname-to-address records", "hostname aliases", "all of the mentioned"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "The domain name system is maintained by _______", answers: ["distributed database system", "a single server", "a single computer", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 1},
    {level:"2", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "Wildcard domain names start with label _____", answers: ["@", "*", "&", "#"], correct: 2},
    /****************************************** 		level 3 ----------- IP_DNS 		******************************************/
    {level:"3", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "How many version /s of IP’s are there?", answers: ["4 Versions", "3 Versions", "2 Versions", "1 version"], correct: 3},
    {level:"3", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "Many desktops and operating systems include which protocol?", answers: ["IPv6 protocol", "IPv4 protocol", "Both IPv6 and IPv4 protocol", "IPv3 protocol"], correct: 1},
    {level:"3", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "The design of the Internet protocol suites adhere to the ________ principle.", answers: ["Data corruption", "End to End principle", "Connection oriented", "Reliability"], correct: 2},
    {level:"3", theme: "IP_DNS", question: " ___________ adjusts the segment size to be smaller than MTU.", answers: ["Internet Protocol 6", "User Datagram Protocol", "Internet Protocol 4", "Transmission Control Protocol"], correct: 4},   
    {level:"3", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "MAC stands for ________", answers: ["Media Area Control", "Memory Access Control", "Memory Area Control", "Media Access Control"], correct: 4},
    {level:"3", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "Hardware address is known as ________", answers: ["MAC address", "IP Address", "Network Interface Card", "Address Resolution Protocol"], correct: 1},
    {level:"3", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "What translates IP address into MAC address?", answers: ["Organizationally Unique Identifier", "Address Resolution Protocol", "Network interface card", "Burned In Address"], correct: 3},
    /****************************************** 		level 4 ----------- IP_DNS 		******************************************/
    {level:"4", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "What is the format of IP address?", answers: ["34 bit", "64 bit", "16 bit", "32 bit"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "Version 6 of IP address has how many bits.", answers: ["64 bits", "128 bits", "32 bits", "256 bits"], correct: 2},
    {level:"4", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "IANA stands for __________", answers: ["Internet Assigned Numbers Authority", "Internal Assigned Numbers Authority", "Internet Associative Numbers Authoritative", "Internal Associative Numbers Authority"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "How many version /s of IP’s are there?", answers: ["4 Versions", "3 Versions", "2 Versions", "1 version"], correct: 3},
    {level:"4", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "Many desktops and operating systems include which protocol?", answers: ["IPv6 protocol", "IPv4 protocol", "Both IPv6 and IPv4 protocol", "IPv3 protocol"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "DNS database contains _______", answers: ["Name server records", "hostname-to-address records", "hostname aliases", "all of the mentioned"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "The domain name system is maintained by _______", answers: ["distributed database system", "a single server", "a single computer", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 1},
    /****************************************** 		level 5 ----------- IP_DNS 		******************************************/
    {level:"5", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "How many version /s of IP’s are there?", answers: ["4 Versions", "3 Versions", "2 Versions", "1 version"], correct: 3},
    {level:"5", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "Many desktops and operating systems include which protocol?", answers: ["IPv6 protocol", "IPv4 protocol", "Both IPv6 and IPv4 protocol", "IPv3 protocol"], correct: 1},
    {level:"5", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "The design of the Internet protocol suites adhere to the ________ principle.", answers: ["Data corruption", "End to End principle", "Connection oriented", "Reliability"], correct: 2},
    {level:"5", theme: "IP_DNS", question: " ___________ adjusts the segment size to be smaller than MTU.", answers: ["Internet Protocol 6", "User Datagram Protocol", "Internet Protocol 4", "Transmission Control Protocol"], correct: 4},   
    {level:"5", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "MAC stands for ________", answers: ["Media Area Control", "Memory Access Control", "Memory Area Control", "Media Access Control"], correct: 4},
    {level:"5", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "Hardware address is known as ________", answers: ["MAC address", "IP Address", "Network Interface Card", "Address Resolution Protocol"], correct: 1},
    {level:"5", theme: "IP_DNS", question: "What translates IP address into MAC address?", answers: ["Organizationally Unique Identifier", "Address Resolution Protocol", "Network interface card", "Burned In Address"], correct: 3},
    
    
    
    /****************************************** 		level 1 ----------- InterviewQs		******************************************/
    {level:"1", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Which is not a part of cyber attacks?", answers: ["bullying", "Malvertising", "MITM", "Ransomeware"], correct: 1},
    {level:"1", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Cybersecurity includes _______ ?", answers: ["Application Security", "Disaster Security", "Operational Security", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"1", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "what types of attacks made on Confidentiality?", answers: ["Cracking encrypted Data", "Doxxing", "Both a and b", "None of the above"], correct: 3},
    {level:"1", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "what types of attacks made on Integrity?", answers: ["Web Penetration", "Doxxing", "Disrupting Server", "Installing the spyware"], correct: 1},
    {level:"1", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Which is not a part of Countermeasure of Confidentiality attacks?", answers: ["Access control", "Hashing", "Biometric Verification", "Encryption"], correct: 2},
    {level:"1", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "what types of attacks made on Availability?", answers: ["DDoS Attacks", "Ransomeware Attacks", "Disrupting Server", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"1", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "What types of Countermeasure for attacks on availability?", answers: ["Regular Backup", "Cryptography", "Hashing", "Access Control"], correct: 1},
    /****************************************** 		level 2 ----------- InterviewQs		******************************************/
    {level:"2", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Which of the following is one of the Cyber Security Goals?", answers: ["Protect the confidentiality of data", "Preserve the integrity of data", "Promote the availability of data for authorized users", "All of the above"], correct: 1},
    {level:"2", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "In cybersecurity, what does CIA stand for?", answers: ["Confidentiality, Confidentiality, Availability", "Central, Intelligence, Agency", "Cybersecurity, Investigation, Agency", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 1},
    {level:"2", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Cybersecurity Protect against what?", answers: ["Unauthorised Access", "Unauthorised Deletion", "Unauthorised Modification", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "When integrity is lacking in a security system, _________ occurs.", answers: ["Database hacking", "Data deletion", "Data tampering", "Data leakage"], correct: 3},
    {level:"2", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Cybersecurity is primarily about?", answers: ["technologies", "processes", "Both a and b", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 3},
    {level:"2", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "What are the key features of Cybersecurity?", answers: ["Vulnerability", "Threat", "Risk", "All of the Above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"2", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "According to the CIA Triad, which of the below-mentioned element is not considered in the triad?", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Authenticity", "Availability", "Integrity"], correct: 2},
    /****************************************** 		level 3 ----------- InterviewQs 		******************************************/
    {level:"3", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "When you use the word _____ it means you are protecting your data from getting disclosed.", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Authentication", "Availabilit"], correct: 1},
    {level:"3", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "______ means the protection of data from modification by unknown users", answers: [" Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Availability", " Non-repudiation"], correct: 2},
    {level:"3", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Cybersecurity encompass the full range of?", answers: ["vulnerability reduction", "incident response", "recovery policies", "All of the above"], correct: 4},
    {level:"3", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Which of the following information security technology is used for avoiding browser-based hacking?", answers: ["Anti-malware in browsers", "Remote browser access", "Adware remover in browsers", "Incognito mode in a browser"], correct: 2},
    {level:"3", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "In which year, the first computer worm (virus) created?", answers: ["1969", "1971", "1970", "1973"], correct: 3},
    {level:"3", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "This helps in identifying the origin of information and authentic user. This referred to here as ________", answers: ["Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Authenticity", "Availability"], correct: 3},
    {level:"3", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Using _____________ for doing competitive information gathering is a crime.", answers: ["Spyware", "Antivirus", "Anti-malware", "Adware"], correct: 1},   
    /****************************************** 		level 4 ----------- InterviewQs 		******************************************/
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "What is the format of IP address?", answers: ["34 bit", "64 bit", "16 bit", "32 bit"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Version 6 of IP address has how many bits.", answers: ["64 bits", "128 bits", "32 bits", "256 bits"], correct: 2},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "IANA stands for __________", answers: ["Internet Assigned Numbers Authority", "Internal Assigned Numbers Authority", "Internet Associative Numbers Authoritative", "Internal Associative Numbers Authority"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "How many version /s of IP’s are there?", answers: ["4 Versions", "3 Versions", "2 Versions", "1 version"], correct: 3},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Many desktops and operating systems include which protocol?", answers: ["IPv6 protocol", "IPv4 protocol", "Both IPv6 and IPv4 protocol", "IPv3 protocol"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "DNS database contains _______", answers: ["Name server records", "hostname-to-address records", "hostname aliases", "all of the mentioned"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "The domain name system is maintained by _______", answers: ["distributed database system", "a single server", "a single computer", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 1},
    /****************************************** 		level 5 ----------- InterviewQs 		******************************************/
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "What is the format of IP address?", answers: ["34 bit", "64 bit", "16 bit", "32 bit"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Version 6 of IP address has how many bits.", answers: ["64 bits", "128 bits", "32 bits", "256 bits"], correct: 2},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "IANA stands for __________", answers: ["Internet Assigned Numbers Authority", "Internal Assigned Numbers Authority", "Internet Associative Numbers Authoritative", "Internal Associative Numbers Authority"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "How many version /s of IP’s are there?", answers: ["4 Versions", "3 Versions", "2 Versions", "1 version"], correct: 3},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "Many desktops and operating systems include which protocol?", answers: ["IPv6 protocol", "IPv4 protocol", "Both IPv6 and IPv4 protocol", "IPv3 protocol"], correct: 1},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "DNS database contains _______", answers: ["Name server records", "hostname-to-address records", "hostname aliases", "all of the mentioned"], correct: 4},
    {level:"4", theme: "InterviewQs", question: "The domain name system is maintained by _______", answers: ["distributed database system", "a single server", "a single computer", "None of the mentioned"], correct: 1},
    
    ];